GARRETT STEED

A driven professional with current knowledge of enterprise sales and needs, analytics/application markets and the current innovations underway across different channels and networks. Adaptable and experienced with selling activities a wide variety of products with a proven track record of success. Consistently meets and exceeds corporate sales goals, while also managing accounts, customers and contracts.

PHONE

571-279-5457



EMAIL

steed.garrett@gmail.com



/linkedin.com/in/garrett-steed-b6859534/

EXPERIENCE



ADOBE

SEPT 2017 -PRESENT BOULDER, CO

Inside Account Manager

- Newly created role supporting and transitioning new eCommerce/Magento acquisition.
- Achieved over 93% individual quota in 2019.
- Managed renewals (over 100% attainment in2018 and 2017) with cross-selling and upselling.
- Supported Government, B2B and B2C, Manufacturing and much more.
- * Sold SaaS LMS and Collaboration tools through multiple partner channels in 2017-2018.



ADOBE

MARCH 2015-SEPT 2017 WASHINGTON D.C.

Senior Account Development Manager

- \$2.4 million pipeline created in 3 quarters 2017.
- * Sold Enterprise SaaS solutions including: Analytics, Adaptive Forms, Asset Management, etc.
- Worked with up to 9 Account Executives with quotes ranging up to \$13 million dollars.
- Supported Federal Civilian and Law Enforcement (VA, HHS, DHS, FBI, DoE and many more). Built
- and maintained existing contracts and renewals and upselling accounts when available.



ENVIRONMENTAL PROTECTION AGENCY

JAN 2014 -MARCH 2015 WASHINGTON D.C.

ORISE Fellow

- Supported the Clean WaterState Revolving Fund. 118.7 billion to communities since 1987 with 38,450 low cost loans across the nation.
- * Provided enterprise in private public partnerships a government service or private business venture that is funded and operated through a partnership of government and one or more private sector companies.



GREAT BASIN INSTITUTE

FEB 2012-OCT 2013 RENO, NV

AMERICORPS - Habitat Field Technician

Gained valuable field experience while working on habitat improvement, and habitat restoration, with the United States Forest Service, Bureau of Land Management, National Park Service, and other agencies.

GREEN STREETS LLC

JUNE 2011 - JAN 2012 BELLEVUE, KY

Consultant

- * Sold sustainable retail items to deal with storm water mitigation to small businesses and organizations.
- Worked within a Tri-State Environmental group for cross channel business.

EDUCATION

ACCOMPLISHMENTS TRAINING

OHIO UNIVERSITY, ATHENS - 2011

Bachelor of Science, Environmental Geography Environmental Studies Certificate Minor in History

Awarded by ExecutiveVice

President for assisting with \$3M HHS Contract

Quota met or exceeded every quarter since start of employment in 2015

Value Selling Associates -Adobe 2017

SFDC/Salesforce: Advanced Microsoft Office: Advanced

Adobe Technical Selling - Summer 2016 Biological Technique Survey Lead - Costa

Rica, 2011

Adobe Captivate: Core Skills: 2018